Preliminary Guide to the Grosvenor Chapman papers, 1931-1994 MS2181
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Organizations, 1956-1994; Series 6
  - C.A.G. Board [Citizens Association of Georgetown], 1977-1978; Series 6 (Box 30, Folder Folder 1)
  - C.A.G. Court of Appeals [Citizens Association of Georgetown], 1978 January 11 -1978 January 17; Series 6 (Box 30, Folder Folder 2)
  - C.A.G. Court of Appeals [Citizens Association of Georgetown], 1978-1986; Series 6 (Box 3, Folder Folder 9)
  - C.A.G. Fine Arts panel [Citizens Association of Georgetown], 1973-1979; Series 6 (Box 3, Folder Folder 8)
  - C.A.G. Fine Arts: legal [Citizens Association of Georgetown], 1974-1975; Series 6 (Box 18, Folder Folder 3)
  - C.A.G. General [Citizens Association of Georgetown], 1978-1986; Series 6 (Box 3, Folder Folder 13)
  - C.A.G. Historic Landmark and Historic District Protection Act [Citizens Association of Georgetown], 1985-1988; Series 6 (Box 33, Folder Folder 10)
  - C.A.G. Lower K St. [Citizens Association of Georgetown], 1991 February 11; Series 6 (Box 32, Folder Folder 4)
  - C.A.G. membership meeting [Citizens Association of Georgetown], 1989-1991; Series 6 (Box 12, Folder Folder 4)
  - C.A.G. newsletter [Citizens Association of Georgetown], 1975-1976; Series 6 (Box 3, Folder Folder 14)
  - C.A.G. Opinion Poll [Citizens Association of Georgetown], 1984-1985; Series 6 (Box 28, Folder Folder 12)
  - C.A.G. parking [Citizens Association of Georgetown], 1985-1992; Series 6 (Box 12, Folder Folder 5)
  - C.A.G. planning [Citizens Association of Georgetown], 1979; Series 6 (Box 3, Folder Folder 15)
  - C.A.G. press media [Citizens Association of Georgetown], 1972 March 28; Series 6 (Box 19, Folder Folder 11)
  - C.A.G. Roads Subcommittee testimony [Citizens Association of Georgetown], 1977-1979; Series 6 (Box 2, Folder Folder 2)
  - C.A.G. Scow [Citizens Association of Georgetown], 1978-1979; Series 6 (Box 2, Folder Folder 4)
  - C.A.G. Scow Task Force [Citizens Association of Georgetown], 1978; Series 6 (Box 2, Folder Folder 5)
  - C.A.G. Scow Task Force [Citizens Association of Georgetown], 1978-1979; Series 6 (Box 2, Folder Folder 6)
  - C.A.G. Scow Task Force: area computations [Citizens Association of Georgetown], 1983-1984; Series 6 (Box 33, Folder Folder 3)
  - C.A.G. Transportation [Citizens Association of Georgetown], 1977 December 22; Series 6 (Box 30, Folder Folder 5)
  - C.A.G. vs Zoning Commission [Citizens Association of Georgetown], 1978; Series 6 (Box 30, Folder Folder 3)
  - C.A.G. vs Zoning Commission Court of Appeals [Citizens Association of Georgetown], 1972; Series 6 (Box 31, Folder Folder 1)
  - C.A.G. vs Zoning Commission joint appendix volume I [Citizens Association of Georgetown], 1972; Series 6 (Box 31, Folder Folder 2)
  - CAG law suit press [Citizens Association of Georgetown], undated; Series 6 (Box 18, Folder Folder 11)
  - C.A.G. vs Zoning Commission joint appendix volume IV [Citizens Association of Georgetown], 1972; Series 6 (Box 31, Folder Folder 3)
  - C.A.G. vs Zoning Commission joint appendix volume V [Citizens Association of Georgetown], 1978; Series 6 (Box 30, Folder Folder 4)
  - C.A.G. vs Zoning Commission Judge Bacon's decision [Citizens Association of Georgetown], 1977; Series 6 (Box 31, Folder Folder 4)
  - C.A.G. vs Zoning Commission plantiffs reply memo [Citizens Association of Georgetown], 1971 February -1975; Series 6 (Box 21, Folder Folder 3)
  - C.A.G. Waterfront activity [Citizens Association of Georgetown], 1991; Series 6 (Box 32, Folder Folder 8)
  - Citizens Association of Georgetown President's agenda for meetings, 1973; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder Folder 12)
  - C.A.G. Whitehurst freeway meeting [Citizens Association of Georgetown], 1978-1979; Series 6 (Box 2, Folder Folder 9)
  - Press clippings non-C.A.G. generated [Citizens Association of Georgetown], undated; Series 6 (Box 25, Folder Folder 12)
  - C.A.G. Zoning: Case 78-1 [Citizens Association of Georgetown], 1967-1990; Series 6 (Box 1, Folder Folder 8)
  - C.F.A. [U.S. Commission of Fine Arts], 1979 December 11; Series 6 (Box 1, Folder Folder 9)
  - C.F.A. [U.S. Commission of Fine Arts], 1977; Series 6 (Box 4, Folder Folder 12)
  - C.O.G. [Council of Government], undated; Series 6 (Box 24, Folder Folder 10)
  - Canal and Riverside Council, 1968-1973; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder Folder 3)
  - Charlestown S.C. Historic Preservation Committee, 1976; Series 6 (Box 18, Folder Folder 1)
  - Coalition for Clean Air, 1976; Series 6 (Box 19, Folder Folder 9)
  - Commitee of 100, 1965-1966; Series 6 (Box 40, Folder Folder 6)
  - Committe of 100 Appeals drive S.C.O.W. [Sailing Club of Washington], 1973-1975; Series 6 (Box 40, Folder Folder 3)
  - Committee of 100, 1960-1961; Series 6 (Box 39, Folder Folder 13)
  - Committee of 100 committee on roads, 1970; Series 6 (Box 39, Folder Folder 1)
  - Committee of 100 - Whitehurst freeway, 1989-1990; Series 6 (Box 32, Folder Folder 9)
  - Committee of 100 1961 file, 1961-1963; Series 6 (Box 39, Folder Folder 12)
  - Committee of 100 board, 1972-1977; Series 6 (Box 41, Folder Folder 1)
  - Committee of 100 board, 1981-1983; Series 6 (Box 40, Folder Folder 10)
  - Committee of 100 board, 1969-1970; Series 6 (Box 37, Folder Folder 3)
  - Committee of 100 board, 1971-1972; Series 6 (Box 37, Folder Folder 4)
  - Committee of 100 bylaws, 1981; Series 6 (Box 40, Folder Folder 14)
  - Committee of 100 correspondence, 1960-1973; Series 6 (Box 40, Folder Folder 4)
  - Committee of 100 correspondence, 1968-1969; Series 6 (Box 38, Folder Folder 3)
  - Committee of 100 correspondence, 1969; Series 6 (Box 38, Folder Folder 4)
  - Committee of 100 correspondence, 1970; Series 6 (Box 38, Folder Folder 5)
  - Committee of 100 current action file, 1963-1965; Series 6 (Box 40, Folder Folder 5)
  - Committee of 100 current file, 1963-1965; Series 6 (Box 40, Folder Folder 15)
  - Committee of 100 explanation of graph, 1968 February 24; Series 6 (Box 42, Folder Folder 8)
  - Committee of 100 freeway, 1967-1968; Series 6 (Box 39, Folder Folder 2)
  - Committee of 100 freeway materials, 1971; Series 6 (Box 42, Folder Folder 9)
  - Committee of 100 historical record of minutes on Whitehurst Freeway, undated; Series 6 (Box 33, Folder Folder 1)
  - Committee of 100 James Deane incident, 1968-1969; Series 6 (Box 39, Folder Folder 14)
  - Committee of 100 Lafayette Square preservation, 1961-1994; Series 6 (Box 40, Folder Folder 1)
  - Committee of 100 lawsuit, undated; Series 6 (Box 39, Folder Folder 8)
  - Committee of 100 legal fund, 1969-1971; Series 6 (Box 38, Folder Folder 6)
  - Committee of 100 long range clothing, 1972; Series 6 (Box 37, Folder Folder 7)
  - Committee of 100 meeting minutes, 1988-1992; Series 6 (Box 12, Folder Folder 3)
  - Committee of 100 membership and board meetings, 1983-1984; Series 6 (Box 40, Folder Folder 8)
  - Committee of 100 mintues, 1974-1983; Series 6 (Box 41, Folder Folder 2)
  - Committee of 100 minutes, 1968 December 19; Series 6 (Box 42, Folder Folder 1)
  - Committee of 100 minutes, 1962-1974; Series 6 (Box 40, Folder Folder 12)
  - Committee of 100 minutes, 1967-1970; Series 6 (Box 37, Folder Folder 5)
  - Committee of 100 minutes, 1970-1972; Series 6 (Box 37, Folder Folder 6)
  - Committee of 100 minutes, 1971-1973; Series 6 (Box 37, Folder Folder 7)
  - Committee of 100 miscellaneous materials, 1961-1995; Series 6 (Box 12, Folder Folder 8)
  - Committee of 100 next meeting, 1967-1981; Series 6 (Box 40, Folder Folder 11)
  - Committee of 100 on the Federal Ciry Zoning and Urban Renewal, 1967-1969; Series 6 (Box 39, Folder Folder 5)
  - Committee of 100 on the Federal City long range planning, undated; Series 6 (Box 38, Folder Folder 1)
  - Committee of 100 on the Federal City Transportation, 1967-1970; Series 6 (Box 39, Folder Folder 6)
  - Committee of 100 organization, 1965-1969; Series 6 (Box 38, Folder Folder 7)
  - Committee of 100 PIPA (Public Interest Planning Assistance program), 1972-1973; Series 6 (Box 41, Folder Folder 4)
  - Committee of 100 preservation, 1965; Series 6 (Box 39, Folder Folder 11)
  - Committee of 100 public hearing on Route I-66, 1970 December 7; Series 6 (Box 42, Folder Folder 4)
  - Committee of 100 public relations, 1968-1970; Series 6 (Box 42, Folder Folder 7)
  - Committee of 100 purpose, 1970; Series 6 (Box 38, Folder Folder 8)
  - Committee of 100 roads, 1969; Series 6 (Box 39, Folder Folder 3)
  - Committee of 100 Roads public opinon and surveys, 1964; Series 6 (Box 42, Folder Folder 5)
  - Committee of 100 self reassessment, 1959-1962; Series 6 (Box 40, Folder Folder 9)
  - Committee of 100 Special Account, 1973-1981; Series 6 (Box 41, Folder Folder 5)
  - Committee of 100 sub committee appearance and preservation, 1972-1974; Series 6 (Box 39, Folder Folder 10)
  - Committee of 100 taxes law, 1970; Series 6 (Box 41, Folder Folder 6)
  - Committee of 100 Tramsportation Issues, 1983-1984; Series 6 (Box 41, Folder Folder 3)
  - Committee of 100 Trustees, 1965-1968; Series 6 (Box 38, Folder Folder 2)
  - Committee of 100 Washington Preservation Conference, 1969-1972; Series 6 (Box 40, Folder Folder 7)
  - Committee of 100 WMATA Traffic Forecast review [Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority], 1967-1968; Series 6 (Box 39, Folder Folder 4)
  - Committee of 100 zoning, 1978; Series 6 (Box 40, Folder Folder 13)
  - Letter to Committee of 100, 1975-1976; Series 6 (Box 4, Folder Folder 15)
  - Comission of Fine Arts membership appointments, 1989-1990; Series 6 (Box 33, Folder Folder 4)
  - D.C. D.P.W. [District of Columbia Department of Public Works], 1985 May 20; Series 6 (Box 44, Folder Folder 7)
  - D.C. Preservation League notes, 1983; Series 6 (Box 28, Folder Folder 11)
  - East End restudy, 1972; Series 6 (Box 19, Folder Folder 8)
  - ECTC and NCTC [National Conference on the Transportation Crisis], 1966-1974; Series 6 (Box 19, Folder Folder 7)
  - Emergency Committee on the Transportation Crisis, 1966-1969; Series 6 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Endorsements, 1971 March 1; Series 6 (Box 21, Folder Folder 1)
  - Feasibility Study C.A.G. special meeting, 1981; Series 6 (Box 41, Folder Folder 7)
  - Foundation for the Preservation of Historic Georgetown, undated; Series 6 (Box 19, Folder Folder 10)
  - G.P.C. Calendar [Georgetown Planning Council], 1964-1965; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder Folder 3)
  - G.P.C. borings [Georgetown Planning Council], 1967; Series 6 (Box 15, Folder Folder 1)
  - G.P.C. chapter and by-laws [Georgetown Planning Council], 1965-1966; Series 6 (Box 15, Folder Folder 5)
  - G.P.C. complete report for P.A.C. [Georgetown Planning Council], 1965-1967; Series 6 (Box 15, Folder Folder 8)
  - G.P.C. conference and testimony [Georgetown Planning Council], 1970-1971; Series 6 (Box 14, Folder Folder 8)
  - G.P.C. correspondence [Georgetown Planning Council], 1967; Series 6 (Box 15, Folder Folder 9)
  - G.P.C. correspondence [Georgetown Planning Council], 1965-1966; Series 6 (Box 15, Folder Folder 10)
  - G.P.C. correspondence [Georgetown Planning Council], 1963-1966; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder Folder 1)
  - G.P.C. highway and D.C. departments [Georgetown Planning Council], 1965-1967; Series 6 (Box 15, Folder Folder 3)
  - G.P.C. history [Georgetown Planning Council], 1965-1969; Series 6 (Box 15, Folder Folder 2)
  - G.P.C. history calendar [Georgetown Planning Council], 1965-1966; Series 6 (Box 15, Folder Folder 14)
  - G.P.C. land use [Georgetown Planning Council], 1966-1967; Series 6 (Box 43, Folder Folder 6)
  - G.P.C. Law suit [1 of 2] [Georgetown Presbyterian Church], 1966-1967; Series 6 (Box 43, Folder Folder 7)
  - G.P.C. Law suit [2 of 2] [Georgetown Presbyterian Church], 1967-1969; Series 6 (Box 15, Folder Folder 12)
  - G.P.C. legislation [Georgetown Planning Council], 1969-1970; Series 6 (Box 14, Folder Folder 7)
  - G.P.C. minutes [Georgetown Planning Council], 1967-1969; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder Folder 6)
  - G.P.C. minutes copies [1 of 2] [Georgetown Planning Council], 1965-1966; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder Folder 7)
  - G.P.C. minutes copies [2 of 2] [Georgetown Planning Council], 1966-1967; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder Folder 8)
  - G.P.C. miscellaneous copies [Georgetown Planning Council], undated; Series 6 (Box 43, Folder Folder 5)
  - G.P.C. names [Georgetown Presbyterian Church], 1969-1971; Series 6 (Box 14, Folder Folder 6)
  - G.P.C. next meeting [Georgetown Planning Council], 1964-1966; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder Folder 5)
  - G.P.C. obsolete material [Georgetown Planning Council], 1966; Series 6 (Box 16, Folder Folder 2)
  - G.P.C. planning commission [Georgetown Planning Council], 1968; Series 6 (Box 14, Folder Folder 9)
  - G.P.C. planning council correspondence [Georgetown Planning Council], 1966; Series 6 (Box 15, Folder Folder 11)
  - G.P.C. presentation to Federation of Garden Clubs [Georgetown Planning Council], 1967-1972; Series 6 (Box 43, Folder Folder 3)
  - G.P.C. Press Publicity: Council and Waterfront [Georgetown Presbyterian Church], 1967-1972; Series 6 (Box 43, Folder Folder 2)
  - G.P.C. Press Publicity: Council and Waterfront [1 of 2] [Georgetown Presbyterian Church], 1965-1968; Series 6 (Box 44, Folder Folder 1)
  - G.P.C. related events and news [Georgetown Presbyterian Church], 1965-1968; Series 6 (Box 15, Folder Folder 4)
  - G.P.C. reports [Georgetown Planning Council], 1965; Series 6 (Box 15, Folder Folder 7)
  - G.P.C. Task Force presentation [Georgetown Planning Council], 1965; Series 6 (Box 15, Folder Folder 13)
  - G.P.C. Task Force report [Georgetown Planning Council], 1965-1966; Series 6 (Box 15, Folder Folder 6)
  - G.P.C. Udall report [Georgetown Planning Council], 1976-1977; Series 6 (Box 4, Folder Folder 13)
  - Georgetown University, 1973-1976; Series 6 (Box 21, Folder Folder 7)
  - Interior Department, 1990 November 19; Series 6 (Box 32, Folder Folder 10)
  - M.P.O. correspondence Kirk and Ben's testimony [Municipal Planning Office], 1976; Series 6 (Box 5, Folder Folder 1)
  - M.P.O. documents [Municipal Planning Office], 1977; Series 6 (Box 4, Folder Folder 18)
  - M.P.O. land use [Municipal Planning Office], 1976-1978; Series 6 (Box 4, Folder Folder 14)
  - M.P.O. taskforce [Municipal Planning Office], 1960-1966; Series 6 (Box 13, Folder Folder 8)
  - N.C.P.C. [National Capital Planning Commission], 1971-1975; Series 6 (Box 23, Folder Folder 12)
  - N.C.P.C. and Coord. committee correspondence [National Capital Planning Commission], 1972 October 18; Series 6 (Box 23, Folder Folder 1)
  - N.C.P.C. and Coord. committee meeting [National Capital Planning Commission], 1971-1974; Series 6 (Box 23, Folder Folder 11)
  - N.C.P.C. conortium [National Capital Planning Commission], 1973 November 6 - 1973 November 29; Series 6 (Box 23, Folder Folder 2)
  - N.C.P.C. Coord. committee meeting [National Capital Planning Commission], 1974 July 16; Series 6 (Box 23, Folder Folder 3)
  - N.C.P.C. coord. committee meeting [National Capital Planning Commission], 1974 April 16; Series 6 (Box 23, Folder Folder 13)
  - N.C.P.C. Coord. committee meeting ( on Rody Sec. development plan) [National Capital Planning Commission], 1972-1973; Series 6 (Box 23, Folder Folder 14)
  - N.C.P.C. Coord. committee meetings Waterfronts [National Capital Planning Commission], 1972-1975; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder Folder 15)
  - N.C.P.C. notices [National Capital Planning Commission], 1975 July 25; Series 6 (Box 23, Folder Folder 5)
  - N.C.P.C. official plan [National Capital Planning Commission], 1972-1973; Series 6 (Box 23, Folder Folder 4)
  - N.C.P.C. Phase I report [National Capital Planning Commission], 1973 July 25; Series 6 (Box 23, Folder Folder 7)
  - N.C.P.C. Phase IIA report [National Capital Planning Commission], 1974-1977; Series 6 (Box 23, Folder Folder 8)
  - N.C.P.C. Phase IIB III [National Capital Planning Commission], 1974 May 1; Series 6 (Box 23, Folder Folder 6)
  - N.C.P.C. testimoney S.C.O.W. [National Capital Planning Commission], 1975 February 6; Series 6 (Box 23, Folder Folder 9)
  - N.C.P.C. testimony G.P.C. phase III [National Capital Planning Commission], 1971-1973; Series 6 (Box 29, Folder Folder 1)
  - National Capital Planning Commission correspondence, undated; Series 6 (Box 28, Folder Folder 13)
  - National Park Service, 1974; Series 6 (Box 19, Folder Folder 4)
  - Office of Municiple Planning, 1979; Series 6 (Box 2, Folder Folder 11)
  - P.U.D. [Planned Unit Development], 1973; Series 6 (Box 25, Folder Folder 11)
  - Petition, 1973-1975; Series 6 (Box 25, Folder Folder 14)
  - S.C.O.W. speeches [Sailing Club of Washington], 1976; Series 6 (Box 26, Folder Folder 7)
  - Correspondence with District Scow, 1972-1975; Series 6 (Box 18, Folder Folder 13)
  - Freeway: Scow [Sailing Club of Washington], 1965; Series 6 (Box 14, Folder Folder 5)
  - Mintues SCOW [Sailing Club of Washington], 1972 December 4; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder Folder 14)
  - Street designs S.C.O.W. [Sailing Club of Washington], 1973 April; Series 6 (Box 26, Folder Folder 9)
  - S.C.O.W. statistics [Sailing Club of Washington], 1973-1979; Series 6 (Box 26, Folder Folder 6)
  - Waterfront Park Scow, 1975-1978; Series 6 (Box 2, Folder Folder 8)
  - S.M.D. correspondence [Single Member District], 1976; Series 6 (Box 4, Folder Folder 7)
  - Special membership meeting advisory committee on the Georgetown Waterfront, 1971 March 1; Series 6 (Box 21, Folder Folder 2)
  - Talk to preservation group, 1985; Series 6 (Box 13, Folder Folder 4)
  - W.A.C.C. board [Wisconsin Avenue Corridor Committee], undated; Series 6 (Box 2, Folder Folder 13)
  - W.A.C.C. directory [Wisconsin Avenue Corridor Committee], 1979; Series 6 (Box 2, Folder Folder 12)
  - W.A.C.C. land use A.N.C. plans [Wisconsin Avenue Corridor Committee], undated; Series 6 (Box 2, Folder Folder 14)
  - W.A.C.C. Preservation [Wisconsin Avenue Corridor Committee], 1977-1979; Series 6 (Box 3, Folder Folder 1)
  - W.B.C. Planning and Zoning Committee, 1960-1961; Series 6 (Box 5, Folder Folder 9)
  - W.P.H.A. Dependability and Quality, 1963; Series 6 (Box 5, Folder Folder 11)
  - W.P.H.A. next meeting Transportation Committee, 1965; Series 6 (Box 6, Folder Folder 4)
  - W.P.H.A. Transportation Committee, 1963-1966; Series 6 (Box 6, Folder Folder 3)
  - W.P.H.A. Transportation Committee correspondence, 1964-1966; Series 6 (Box 6, Folder Folder 6)
  - W.P.H.A. Transportation Committee final report, 1963; Series 6 (Box 6, Folder Folder 7)
  - W.P.H.A. Transportation Committee reference material, 1962-1965; Series 6 (Box 6, Folder Folder 1)
  - W.P.H.A. Transportation Committee references, 1964; Series 6 (Box 6, Folder Folder 8)
  - W.P.H.A. Transportation Committee references, 1965; Series 6 (Box 6, Folder Folder 9)
  - W.P.H.A. Transportation hearings, 1963; Series 6 (Box 6, Folder Folder 5)
  - W.P.H.A. Transportation minutes, 1962-1964; Series 6 (Box 5, Folder Folder 10)
  - W.P.H.A. Transportation next meeting, 1963-1965; Series 6 (Box 6, Folder Folder 2)
  - W.P.H.A. Transportation reports, 1963; Series 6 (Box 5, Folder Folder 12)
  - Washington Planning and Housing Association, 1953-1967; Series 6 (Box 7, Folder Folder 3)
  - Waterfront: correspondence NCPC GC [National Capital Planning Commission], 1970-1971; Series 6 (Box 18, Folder Folder 5)
  - West End, 1983; Series 6 (Box 28, Folder Folder 10)
- People, 1955-1983; Series 7
  - 4805 Dennis Argall, 1977; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Brian McCormick, 1980-1981; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Frederick Gloss, 1976-1977; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Senator Hatfield, 1979-1980; Series 7 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - John F. O'Neill jr., 1980; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Joint statement of Stewart Udall and Mayor Walter Washington, 1969 March; Series 7 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Michael E. Levine, 1979; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Shackletons, 1977; Series 7 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Terry Miller, 1972; Series 7 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - The Highway Men David Hapgood, 1955-1983; Series 7 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Von Eckardt Wolf, 1971-1972; Series 7 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Publicity, 1957-1993; Series 8
  - Blog, undated; Series 8 (Box 32, Folder Folder 1)
  - Bulletin: The Garden Club of America May, 1957; Series 8 (Box 44, Folder Folder 5)
  - Camera magazines photography materials, 1979; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder Folder 4)
  - Chapman and Miller promotional material, 1968; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder Folder 2)
  - Chapman and Miller promotional material, 1968; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder Folder 3)
  - Clippings, 1965-1967; Series 8 (Box 44, Folder Folder 8)
  - Clippings 1974 Biography set 2, 1966-1993; Series 8 (Box 44, Folder Folder 10)
  - Consumer Reports Getting to Work and Back, 1965 January 26; Series 8 (Box 42, Folder Folder 21)
  - Correspondence press and names, 1973-1975; Series 8 (Box 25, Folder Folder 7)
  - The Georgetowner, 1965-1967; Series 8 (Box 35, Folder Folder 1)
  - The Georgetowner, 1967 January 26 - 1967 March 22; Series 8 (Box 35, Folder Folder 2)
  - The Georgetowner, 1971; Series 8 (Box 35, Folder Folder 3)
  - The Georgetowner, 1977 October 6 - 1978 July 14; Series 8 (Box 36, Folder Folder 7)
  - The Georgetowner, 1981 December 21 - 1982 January 21; Series 8 (Box 36, Folder Folder 8)
  - The Georgetowner [1 of 2], 1973 January 11 - 1973 May 15; Series 8 (Box 35, Folder Folder 7)
  - The Georgetowner [1 of 2], 1974 January 9 - 1974 May 11; Series 8 (Box 36, Folder Folder 1)
  - The Georgetowner [1 of 2], 1975 January 8 - 1975 May 11; Series 8 (Box 36, Folder Folder 3)
  - The Georgetowner [1 of 2], 1976 January 7 -1976 April 14; Series 8 (Box 36, Folder Folder 5)
  - The Georgetowner [1 of 3], 1972 February 10 - 1972 April 20; Series 8 (Box 35, Folder Folder 4)
  - The Georgetowner [2 of 2], 1972 November 16 - 1972 December 18; Series 8 (Box 35, Folder Folder 6)
  - The Georgetowner [2 of 2], 1973 May 16 - 1973 November 13; Series 8 (Box 35, Folder Folder 8)
  - The Georgetowner [2 of 2], 1974 May 11 - 1974 December 17; Series 8 (Box 36, Folder Folder 2)
  - The Georgetowner [2 of 2], 1975 June 22 - 1975 September 17; Series 8 (Box 36, Folder Folder 4)
  - The Georgetowner [2 of 2], 1976 May 12 - 1976 May 19; Series 8 (Box 36, Folder Folder 6)
  - The Georgetowner [2 of 3], 1972 May 4 - 1972 October 19; Series 8 (Box 35, Folder Folder 5)
  - Georgetowner, 1976-1978; Series 8 (Box 24, Folder Folder 2)
  - Georgetowner articles by Chapman, 1973-1978; Series 8 (Box 24, Folder Folder 1)
  - Georgetowner past articles, 1971-1974; Series 8 (Box 23, Folder Folder 16)
  - Highway clippings, 1970; Series 8 (Box 17, Folder Folder 2)
  - Magazines the Washingtonian and Parents, 1972-1975; Series 8 (Box 22, Folder Folder 13)
  - Newspaper inconsistencies, 1964-1969; Series 8 (Box 17, Folder Folder 1)
  - Newsweek the Agony of Getting Anywhere, 1967 January 9; Series 8 (Box 42, Folder Folder 22)
  - P.R. Newsletter, 1977-1980; Series 8 (Box 2, Folder Folder 1)
  - Periodical: Architectural Record, 1939 January; Series 8 (Box 9, Folder Folder 16)
  - Periodical: Architecture report, 1963; Series 8 (Box 9, Folder Folder 17)
  - Press, 1980-1986; Series 8 (Box 24, Folder Folder 7)
  - Press C.A.G. generated [Citizens Association of Georgetown], 1975-1976; Series 8 (Box 25, Folder Folder 8)
  - Press C.A.G. generated [Citizens Association of Georgetown], 1972-1974; Series 8 (Box 25, Folder Folder 9)
  - Press clippings, 1990-1991; Series 8 (Box 32, Folder Folder 2)
  - Press clippings legal, 1973-1974; Series 8 (Box 25, Folder Folder 13)
  - Press clippings non C.A.G. [Citizens Association of Georgetown], 1975; Series 8 (Box 25, Folder Folder 4)
  - Press clippings related issues, 1965-1975; Series 8 (Box 25, Folder Folder 2)
  - Press media, 1972-1974; Series 8 (Box 26, Folder Folder 4)
  - Press releases, 1975-1976; Series 8 (Box 25, Folder Folder 1)
  - Press releases designs, undated; Series 8 (Box 44, Folder Folder 14)
  - Press W.E.T.A., undated; Series 8 (Box 25, Folder Folder 10)